Jacob Seidenberg Additional Arbitration Case Files 5217
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Jacob Seidenberg Additional Arbitration Case Files
1983
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Seidenberg, Jacob
5217
17 cubic feet
17 linear ft.
Records (documents), case files.
Chiefly files of cases in the railroad industry, brought before Boards on which Seidenberg served from 1960-1974. The major unions represented in these files are United Transportation Union; Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks; Brotherhood of Railroad Signalmen; Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen; Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen; and Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers. The major railroads represented are Penn Central Transportation Company; Southern Pacific Company; Erie-Lackawanna Railroad Company; Long Island Railroad Company; Atchison, Topeka and Santa Fe Railway Company; Chicago, Milwaukee and St. Paul Railway Company; Norfolk and Western Railway Company; and Southern Buffalo Railway Company. Also, Union Pacific Railway Company; Central Georgia Railroad Company; Illinois Central Gulf Railroad Company; Western Maryland Railway Company; St. Louis South Western Railway Lines; and Monongahela Railway Company.
5556058
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, October 04, 2005
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, February 21, 2017
Biographical / Historical
Dr. Jacob Seidenberg (1914-1996) was a government official who specialized in labor arbitration and non-discrimination contracts, and wrote extensively on labor law and negotiations. He graduated from Temple University in 1937 and received a law degree from the University of Pennsylvania Law School in 1941. During the 1940s he was an attorney with the U.S. War Department, the National War Labor Board and the National Wage Stabilization Board. In 1948 he went to graduate school at Cornell University, from which he earned his Ph.D. in industrial and labor relations in 1951. In 1951 he joined the staff of the President's Committee on Government Contract Compliance. The Committee was abolished by President Dwight D. Eisenhower in August 1953 by Executive Order 10479 and was succeeded by the President's Committee on Government Contracts. Seidenberg was appointed Executive Director of the new committee and served until January 1960 when he resigned to become a full-time labor arbitrator. The Committee was responsible for enforcing non-discrimination clauses in government contracts, worked with private businesses to help them overcome job discrimination, and developed educational programs against ethnic and racial discrimination. The chairman was Vice President Richard Nixon, and the vice chairman was Secretary of Labor James P. Mitchell. In later years Seidenberg served on a number of boards of inquiry involving labor disputes. From 1970 to 1975 he was chairman of the Federal Services Impasses Panel which settled deadlocks in federal labor negotiations.
Scope and Contents
Chiefly files of cases in the railroad industry, brought before Boards on which Seidenberg served from 1960-1974. The major unions represented in these files are United Transportation Union; Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks; Brotherhood of Railroad Signalmen; Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen; Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen; and Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers. The major railroads represented are Penn Central Transportation Company; Southern Pacific Company; Erie-Lackawanna Railroad Company; Long Island Railroad Company; Atchison, Topeka and Santa Fe Railway Company; Chicago, Milwaukee and St. Paul Railway Company; Norfolk and Western Railway Company; and Southern Buffalo Railway Company. Also, Union Pacific Railway Company; Central Georgia Railroad Company; Illinois Central Gulf Railroad Company; Western Maryland Railway Company; St. Louis South Western Railway Lines; and Monongahela Railway Company.
The major issues involved include violation of work assignment rules, dismissal, seniority, discipline, time claims, mileage claims, and payment claims, holiday pay, runaround, wage rates, deadheading, overtime, suspension, compensation, reinstatement, and others. Additionally, there are numerous cases arbitrated by Seidenberg involving the following unions: National Union of Hospital and Health Care Employees; International Brotherhood of Teamsters; United Automobile, Aircraft and Agricultural Implement Workers of America; Office and Professional Employees International Union; American Federation of State, County, and Municipal Employees (AFSCME); Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America; United Brotherhood of Carpenters District Council; United Steelworkers of America; and International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5031 A&B: Jacob Seidenberg Additional Arbitration Files 5032: Jacob Seidenberg Injunction Study 5175: Jacob Seidenberg Taft-Hartley Maritime Dispute Records 5194: Jacob Seidenberg Additional Files 5229: Jacob Seidenberg Additional records 5468: Jacob Seidenberg Arbitration files 5519: Jacob Seidenberg Additional Arbitration Files 5571: Jacob Seidenberg Additional Arbitration Files 5605: Jacob Seidenberg Additional Arbitration Records 5635: Jacob Seidenberg Additional Arbitration Files 5666: Jacob Seidenberg Additional Arbitration Files 5706: Jacob Seidenberg Additional Arbitration Files 5756: Jacob Seidenberg Additional Arbitration Files 5773: Jacob Seidenberg Additional Arbitration Files 5808: Jacob Seidenberg Additional Arbitration Files 5900: Jacob Seidenberg Additional Arbitration Files 5935: Jacob Seidenberg Additional Arbitration Files 5953: Jacob Seidenberg Additional Arbitration Records 5988: Jacob Seidenberg Additional Arbitration Files
Aberdeen Proving Ground (Md.); ABF Freight System; AMF, Inc.; A & P; Acme Markets, Inc.; Aerofin Corp.; AFSCME; Air Wisconsin; Allephany Pepsi-Cola Bottling Co.; Allied Aviation Fueling Co.; Allied Fibers & Plastics; Almo Electronics Group; Altair Airlines, Inc.; Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America; Amana Refrigeration, inc.; Ambac Industries, Inc.; Ambassador Motel; American Bank Stationery Co.; American Export, Inc.; American Merchant Marine Institute; American Postal Workers Hospital Plan; American Totalistic Co.; Arundel County Board of Education; Asarco Inc.; Atchison, Topeka and Santa Fe Railroad Company; Atlantic Coast Line Railroad Company; Auco, Aerostructure Division; Baltimore and Ohio Railroad Company; Bangor & Aroostook Railroad Co.; Bell Telephone Company; Bethesda Health Center; Black & Decker Corporation (Towson, Md.); Blue Diamond; Boston and Maine Railroad; Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers (U.S.); Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen.; Brotherhood of Railroad Signalmen; Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employes; Calvert County Board of Education; Central Transfer Co.; Centrur Home; Charles County Board of Education; Chessie System, inc.; Chicago, Milwaukee, and St. Paul Railway Company; Chicago, Northwestern Railway Co.; Chicago, Rock Island & Pacific Rail Road Co.; Classic Chemical; Cleaver-Brooks (Firm); Conoco, Inc.; Con Rail; Consolidated Freightways, inc.; Corning Glass Works; Crowell Corporation; Crown Zellerback Corporation; Damon Corporation; Delmarva Power Company; Denver and Rio Grande Western Railroad Company; Detroit, Toledo, and Ironton Railroad; District of Columbia; District of Columbia. Police Dept.; Dorchester County Board of Education; Drug Fair; Dupont Company; Eastern Airlines, Inc.; Eaton Corporation; Erie-Lackawanna Railroad Company; Empire Steel Castings; Evans Transportation; Federal Yeast Company; Federation of Professional Athletes; International Association of Fire Fighters; Fisher & Porter Co.; Florida East Coast Highway Dispatch Co.; Food Fair; Freda Corporation; Frontier Airlines; Georgetown University Hospital; Georgia-Pacific Corporation; Giant (Firm); Ginn and Company; Golden Nugget Hotel & Resort; Grand Trunk Railway Company of Canada; Grand Union Company; Greenlawn Classics, Inc.; Grey Concrete Pipe Company Inc.; Hamilton Hotel (Mays Landing, N.J.); Harrah's Hotel & Casino; Harrington Hotel; Hemingway Transport, Inc.; Henry Vogt Machine Company; Hermitite; Hess Oil Corporation; Illinois Central Gulf Railroad; International Air Line Pilots Association; International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers; International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America; International Union, United Automobile, Aircraft, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America; John Sexton & Co.; Kansas City Terminal Railroad Co.; Kash & Karry; Kent County Board of Education; Knoxville Iron Company; Kraft, inc.; Lank Wookwork, Inc.; Lee Rubber & Tire Corporation; Library of Congress; Long Green Nursing Center; Long Island Railroad Company; Louderback Transportation Co.; Maine Central Railroad Company; Major League Baseball Players Association; Marquette Cement Co.; Maryland Classified Employees Association; Mason-Dixon Lines, Inc.; Mead Packaging, Inc.; Meridan Nursing Center; Metromedia, Inc.; Metropolitan Atlantic Rapid Transit Authority; Metropolitan Edison Company; Mobil Corporation; Monogahela Connecting Railroad Co.; Montgomery County Board of Education; Monumental Life Insurance Co.; Mor Flo Industries, Inc.; Morgan Millwork Co.; National Car Rental Systems, inc.; National Gypsum Company; National Rolling Mills; New Castle County (Del.); New York Telephone Company; News American; Norfolk Naval Shipyard (U.S.); Norfolk Southern Railway Company; Olin Mathieson Chemical Corporation; Owens Illinois, Forest Products Division; PPG Industries; Pan Am World Airways, Inc.; Pennsylvania. Liquor Control Board; Pennsylvania Power & Light Company; Pennsylvania Railroad; Pennsylvania Truck Lines, Inc.; Pepsi-Cola Bottling Corp.; Philadelphia Gas Works; Philadelphia Gear Corporation; Prince George's County (Md.). Police Dept.; Prince William Hospital; Printing Industry of Washington D.C.; Provident Hospital (Chicago, Ill.); Publicker Industries Inc.; Purolator Armed Inc.; RCA Corporation; Reisch Trucking Co.; Resorts International Casino Hotel; Reynolds Metal Company; Rollins Outdoor Ad.; Ropes Eastern Corp.; Roubin-Janerio, Inc.; Rudy's Farm Company; Ryder Truck Lines; Safeway Stores, Inc.; Safeway Trails; Schuster Express; Simkin, Industries; Singer Company; Smith Transfer Co.; Southeastern Pennsylvania Transit Authority; Southern Pacific Company; Southern Railway (U.S.); St. Joe Container Corp.; St. Louis and Southwestern Railroad Company; St. Louis and Southeastern Railway Company; St. Mary County Board of Education; Texas International Airlines; Union Boiler Co.; Union Carbide Corporation; Union Pacific Railroad Company; United States. Bureau of Alcohol, Tobacco, and Firearms; U.S. Army Material Development & Readiness Command; United States. Commission on Civil Rights; United States. Department of Commerce.; United States. Department of Defense.; United States. Department of Health and Human Services.; United States Department of Labor; United States. Government Printing Office; United States. Marine Corps.; United States. National Labor Board.; United States. Naval Ordnance Station (Indian Head, Md.); United States. Navy. Air Rework Facility; United States. Navy. Air Station Oceana; United States. Navy. Exchange Service; United States. Park Police.; United States. Patent and Trademark Office; United States. Small Business Administration; United States. Social Security Administration; United States. Veteran Administration Medical Center; Vermont Northern Railroad Company; Virginia-Pilot Ledger Star; WDCA; WJZ-TV; Washington & Gas Light Co.; Washington-Baltimore Newspaper Guild; Washington County Board of Education; Washington Hospital Center; Washington Metropolitan Area Transit Authority; W.D. Byron & Sons, Inc.; Western Pacific Railroad Company; Western Pennsylvania Water Company; Westinghouse Electric Corporation; Winner Distributing; United Workers, Inc.; United Federation of Teachers; United Federation of Teachers. Local 2 (AFT); Cogen, Charles; Dodds, David R.; Lefkowitz, Abraham; Seidenberg, Jacob; Shanker, Albert; Taft, Philip, 1902-; Theobald, John J.
5556058
- ABF Freight (Box 1, Folder 1)
  Scope and Contents
  Local 557, IBT Panel
- ABF Freight System (Box 1, Folder 2)
  Local 557, IBT
- AMF, Inc. (Box 1, Folder 3)
- AMF, Inc. (Box 1, Folder 4)
- A & P, UFCC (Box 1, Folder 5)
  FMCS #81-KO-2663
- A & P, Local 32, IBT (Box 1, Folder 6)
  FMCS #81-KO-9906
- A & P, UFCW Local 400 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  FMCS #82-KO-3534
- Atchison, Topeka & Santa Fe Railway Co. (Box 1, Folder 8)
- ACME, Warehouse Employees Local 169 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- ACME, UFCW Local 1393 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  AAA #14-30-2256-80Q
- ACME, UFCW Local 1357 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  AAA #14-30-1741-82Q
- Aerofin Corp. (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Air Wisconsin (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Allegheny Pepsi-Cola Bottling Co. (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Allied Aviation Fueling Co. (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Allied Fibers & Plastics (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Almo Electronics Group (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Altair Airlines Inc. (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Amana Refrigeration Inc. (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Ambac Industries, Inc. (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Ambassador Hotel (Box 1, Folder 21)
- American Bank Stationery Co. (Box 1, Folder 22)
- American Export, Inc. (Box 1, Folder 23)
- American Merchant Marine Institute (Box 2, Folder 1)
- American Postal Workers Hospital Plan (Box 2, Folder 2)
- American Postal Workers Hospital Plan, Local 2 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  AAA #16-30-0101-82
- American Totalisator Co. (Box 2, Folder 4)
  FMCS #82-KO-8073
- American Totalisator Co. (Box 2, Folder 5)
  FMCS #81-K-12328
- Arundel County, Bd. of Ed. (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Asarco, Inc. (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Atchison, Topeka & Santa Fe Railway [folder 1 of 2] (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Atchison, Topeka & Santa Fe Railway [folder 2 of 2] (Box 2, Folder 9)
  Awards
- Atlantic Coast Line RR Co. (Box 2, Folder 10)
  Division 2
- Avco, Aerostructure Division, Local 735 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  FMCS #82-KO-3293
- Baltimore & Ohio RR (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Baltimore & Ohio RR (Box 2, Folder 13)
  Award no.1742
- Baltimore & Ohio RR (Box 2, Folder 14)
  Awards nos.1733, 1734, 1735, 1736
- Baltimore & Ohio RR (Box 2, Folder 15)
  Award no.1758/PLB no.969
- Baltimore & Ohio RR (Box 2, Folder 16)
  PLB no.969. Awards nos.1806, 1807, 1808, 1809, 1810, 1811, 1812, 1817
- Bangor & Aroostoock RR Co. (Box 2, Folder 17)
  Final Awards
- Bell Telephone Co. (Box 2, Folder 18)
  AAA #14-30-1129-82J
- Bethesda Health Center (Box 2, Folder 19)
  AAA #16-30-0200-83J
- Black & Decker, Inc (Box 2, Folder 20)
  AAA #14-30-0992-81Q
- Blue Diamond Co., Local 557 (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Boston & Maine RR (Box 2, Folder 22)
- Boston & Maine RR (Box 2, Folder 23)
  Interpretation
- Calvert County Board of Education (Box 2, Folder 24)
  AAA #16-39-0165-82
- Calvert County Board of Education (Box 2, Folder 25)
  AAA #16-39-0207-83T
- Central Transfer Co., Local 557 (Box 2, Folder 26)
- Century Home (Box 2, Folder 27)
  AAA #14-30-1471-81F
- Charles County Board of Education (Box 2, Folder 28)
- Chessie System RR (Box 2, Folder 29)
  PLB #3055
- Chicago, Milwaukee, St. Paul and Pacific RR (Box 2, Folder 30)
  PLB #448
- Chicago & North Western Railway Co. (Box 2, Folder 31)
- Chicago Rock Island and Pacific RR Co. (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Classic Chemical (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Cleaver Brooks (Box 3, Folder 3)
  AAA #14-30-1149-83A
- Conoco Inc. (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Consolidated Rail Corp. (ConRail) [folder 1 of 7] (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Consolidated Rail Corp. (ConRail) [folder 2 of 7] (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Consolidated Rail Corp. (ConRail) [folder 3 of 7] (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Consolidated Rail Corp. (ConRail) [folder 4 of 7] (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Consolidated Rail Corp. (ConRail) [folder 5 of 7] (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Consolidated Rail Corp. (ConRail) [folder 6 of 7] (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Consolidated Rail Corp. (ConRail) [folder 7 of 7] (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Consolidated Freightways, Local 557 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Corning Glass Works (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Crowell Corp. (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Crown Zellerback Corp., Local 639 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Damon Corp., District Lodge 67 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Delmarva Power Co. (Box 3, Folder 17)
  FMCS #78-K-21907
- Denver & Rio Grande RR Co. (Box 3, Folder 18)
  PLB n.2776
- Detroit, Toledo & Ironton RR Co. [folder 1 of 2] (Box 3, Folder 19)
- Detroit, Toledo & Ironton RR Co. [folder 2 of 2] (Box 3, Folder 20)
- District of Columbia (Box 4, Folder 1)
  AAA #16-30-0232-80
- Eastern Airlines, Inc. [folder 7 of 12] (Box 5, Folder 1)
- District of Columbia, Public Schools (Box 4, Folder 2)
  AAA #16-30-0199-82
- District of Columbia, Public Schools Council 20 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  AAA #16-39-0162-79
- District of Columbia (Box 4, Folder 4)
  AAA #16-39-0058-81
- District of Columbia (Box 4, Folder 5)
- District of Columbia, Metro Police Department, Local 492 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  AAA #16-39-0222-81
- District of Columbia, Public Schools Council 20 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  AAA #16-39-0276-80
- District of Columbia, Metro Police Department (Box 4, Folder 8)
  AAA #16-39-0159-82
- Dodds, David R., Local 771 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  AAA #14-30-0155-82R
- Dorchester County Board of Education (Box 4, Folder 10)
  AAA #16-39-0037-81
- Drug Fair, Warehouse Employees, Local 730 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  FMCS no.82-KO-18588
- Drug Fair, Warehouse Employees, Local 730 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  FMCS no.83-K-16391
- Dupont Co. [folder 1 of 2] (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Dupont Co. [folder 2 of 2] (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Eastern Airlines, Inc. [folder 1 of 12] (Box 4, Folder 15)
  ALPA Local 5885, EAL-68-64
- Eastern Airlines, Inc. [folder 2 of 12] (Box 4, Folder 16)
- Eastern Airlines, Inc. [folder 3 of 12] (Box 4, Folder 17)
  EAL-105-80
- Eastern Airlines, Inc. [folder 4 of 12] (Box 4, Folder 18)
  EAL-22-73, EAL-16-73, ALPA-19-73, ALPA-18-73
- Eastern Airlines, Inc. [folder 5 of 12] (Box 4, Folder 19)
- Eastern Airlines, Inc. [folder 6 of 12] (Box 4, Folder 20)
- Eastern Airlines, Inc. [folder 8 of 12] (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Eastern Airlines, Inc. [folder 9 of 12] (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Eastern Airlines, Inc. [folder 10 of 12] (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Eastern Airlines, Inc. [folder 11 of 12] (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Eastern Airlines, Inc. [folder 12 of 12] (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Eaton Corp. (Box 5, Folder 7)
  FMCS no.82-K-29289
- Empire Steel Castings (Box 5, Folder 8)
  AAA #14-30-1465-81Q
- Evans Transportation Co., Local 733 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Federal Yeast Co. (Box 5, Folder 10)
  FMCS no.81-K-26208
- Federation of Professional Athletes, Local 2 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Firefighters, International Association of (Box 5, Folder 12)
  FMCS no.82-K-18352
- Fisher & Porter Co. (Box 5, Folder 13)
  AAA #14-30-1735-82R
- Florida East Coast Highway Dispatch Co. (Box 5, Folder 14)
- Florida East Coast Railway Co. (Box 5, Folder 15)
- Food Fair Store, Inc. (Box 5, Folder 16)
- Freda Corp. (Box 5, Folder 17)
- Frontier Airlines, Inc. (Box 5, Folder 18)
- Georgetown University Hospital [folder 1 of 9] (Box 5, Folder 19)
- Georgetown University Hospital [folder 2 of 9] (Box 5, Folder 20)
- Georgetown University Hospital [folder 3 of 9] (Box 5, Folder 21)
- Georgetown University Hospital [folder 4 of 9] (Box 5, Folder 22)
- Georgetown University Hospital [folder 5 of 9] (Box 5, Folder 23)
- Georgetown University Hospital [folder 6 of 9] (Box 5, Folder 24)
- Georgetown University Hospital [folder 7 of 9] (Box 5, Folder 25)
- Georgetown University Hospital [folder 8 of 9] (Box 5, Folder 26)
- Georgetown University Hospital [folder 9 of 9] (Box 5, Folder 27)
- Georgia Pacific Corp. [folder 1 of 2] (Box 5, Folder 28)
- Georgia Pacific Corp. [folder 2 of 2] (Box 5, Folder 29)
- Giant Food, Inc. (Box 5, Folder 30)
- Ginn & Co., Inc. [folder 1 of 2] (Box 5, Folder 31)
- Ginn & Co., Inc. [folder 2 of 2] (Box 5, Folder 32)
- Golden Nugget Hotel & Resort (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Grand Trunk Rail System (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Grand Union Co. (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Greenlawn Classics, Inc. (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Grey Concrete Pipe Co., Inc. (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Hamilton Hotel (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Harrah's Hotel & Casino (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Harrington Hotel (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Hemingway Transport, Inc. (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Henry Vogt Machine Co. (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Hermetite, Div. of Mundet Industries (Box 6, Folder 11)
- Hess Oil Corp. [folderr 1 of 2] (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Hess Oil Corp. [folderr 2 of 2] (Box 6, Folder 13)
- Illinois Central Gulf RR [folder 1 of 7] (Box 6, Folder 14)
- Illinois Central Gulf RR [folder 2 of 7] (Box 6, Folder 15)
- Illinois Central Gulf RR [folder 3 of 7] (Box 6, Folder 16)
- Illinois Central Gulf RR [folder 4 of 7] (Box 6, Folder 17)
- Illinois Central Gulf RR [folder 5 of 7] (Box 6, Folder 18)
- Illinois Central Gulf RR [folder 6 of 7] (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Illinois Central Gulf RR [folder 7 of 7] (Box 7, Folder 2)
- John Sexton & Co. (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Kansas City Terminal RR Co. [folder 1 of 3] (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Kansas City Terminal RR Co. [folder 2 of 3] (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Kansas City Terminal RR Co. [folder 3 of 3] (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Kash and Karry Stores (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Kent County Board of Education (Box 7, Folder 8)
- E.I. DuPont de Nemours and Company Vol. II, 1983 (Box 17, Folder 9)
- Knoxville Iron Co. (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Kraft Inc. (Box 7, Folder 10)
- Lank Woodwork, Inc. (Box 7, Folder 11)
- Lee Rubber & Tire Corp. (Box 7, Folder 12)
- Long Green Nursing Center (Box 7, Folder 13)
- Long Island Railroad [folder 1 of 12] (Box 7, Folder 14)
- Long Island Railroad [folder 2 of 12] (Box 7, Folder 15)
- Long Island Railroad [folder 3 of 12] (Box 7, Folder 16)
- Long Island Railroad [folder 4 of 12] (Box 7, Folder 17)
- Long Island Railroad [folder 5 of 12] (Box 7, Folder 18)
- Long Island Railroad [folder 6 of 12] (Box 7, Folder 19)
- Long Island Railroad [folder 7 of 12] (Box 7, Folder 20)
- Long Island Railroad [folder 8 of 12] (Box 7, Folder 21)
- Long Island Railroad [folder 9 of 12] (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Long Island Railroad [folder 10 of 12] (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Long Island Railroad [folder 11 of 12] (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Long Island Railroad [folder 12 of 12] (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Louderback Transportation Co. (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Maine Central RR Co. (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Major League Baseball Player Relation Committee [folder 1 of 2] (Box 8, Folder 7)
- Major League Baseball Player Relation Committee [folder 2 of 2] (Box 8, Folder 8)
- Marquette Cement Co. (Box 8, Folder 9)
- Maryland Classified Employees Assn. (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Mason-Dixon Lines, Inc. [folder 1 of 2] (Box 8, Folder 11)
- Mason-Dixon Lines, Inc. [folder 2 of 2] (Box 8, Folder 12)
- Mead Packaging, Inc. (Box 8, Folder 13)
- Meridian Nursing Center (Box 8, Folder 14)
- Metromedia, Inc. (Box 8, Folder 15)
- Metropolitan Atlanta Rapid Transit Authority (Box 8, Folder 16)
- Metropolitan Edison Co. [folder 1 of 2] (Box 8, Folder 17)
- Metropolitan Edison Co. [folder 2 of 2] (Box 8, Folder 18)
- Metropolitan Police Dept., Dist. of Columbia [folder 1 of 2] (Box 8, Folder 19)
- Metropolitan Police Dept., Dist. of Columbia [folder 2 of 2] (Box 8, Folder 20)
- Mobil Corp. (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Monongahela Connecting RR Co. [folder 1 of 2] (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Monongahela Connecting RR Co. [folder 2 of 2] (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Montgomery County Board of Education [folder 1 of 2] (Box 9, Folder 4)